Hey. can I get you guys anything
else before I close this check out?
As a matter of
fact. you can.
My partner.
Trapezius Milkington.
would like to see something
in a Belgian waffle.
Shawn. it's 12:30.
I do not want waffles
or eggs or Malt-O-Meal.
All right. What would you recommend?
Oh. my gosh! If you're going to
do this. I'm going to the bathroom.
Excuse me.
Don't mind him. His bladder's
probably smaller than yours.
Now go ahead. and take my taste
buds on a fantastical journey.
I don't know...
I like the burgers.
Ah. ah. ah. I'm sorry.
I should have told you.
Only rule. it can't be something
that someone would order for lunch.
Keep in mind. we want
to go off script here.
Okay. I see. Well. in
that case I would recommend
the pumpkin pancakes
with a side of lingcod.
Does that work?
Let's get married.
You don't even know me!
Oh. really! Allow me
to introduce yourself.
Jetta girl. maybe green.
Backseat loaded with
empty Pinkberry cups.
Oh. my God!
Wrong! I drive a Jeep. A black Jeep.
But you're dead-on
with the Pinkberry.
So what do you think?
Should we set a date or what?
Mmm. I'll think about it.
Fair enough.
Mmm-hmm.
Let me guess.
She's considering your
proposal of marriage?
How could you
possibly know that?
Shawn. you use that
same tired-ass routine
on every other waitress
that serves us.
This is
categorically untrue.
You used it on that 80-year-old
fixings attendant at Fuddruckers.
What's your point. man? My point
is. you're going to be 80 years old
and still shamelessly
hitting on waitresses.
Is that what you want?
Is that a trick question?
What do you think?
All right. Hitch. you want
me to take a chance? Huh?
You want to see some
Will Hunting action?
Here we go.
Who are you
calling? Juliet?
That routine is as tired
as the waitress bit.
Wait for it.
Hello?
Abigail Lytar?
Judd Nelson.
Shawn. stop playing.
Is that really Abigail?
Shawn. is that you?
Of course it is.
Don't be ridiculous.
Look. clearly. we left some loose
ends at our high school reunion.
so I was thinking that
maybe we should get together.
Why on earth would you
think that's a good idea?
Oh. I don't know. the last time I saw
you. we kissed for like 27 seconds?
Can I tell you something? Gord.
So just us.
sitting at the same table?
Hopefully a corner booth.
Abigail. what's
happening here is.
I'm asking you out
on a proper date.
Shawn. are you sure?
Are you sure about this?
Yes. I believe I am.
Pick you up at 7:00.
I'll be the one flaring
my nostrils uncontrollably.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
Oh. God. no.
Done. How do you like them apples?
I sincerely hope you didn't
just do that to prove a point.
She's a real person.
Shawn. That's no joke.
She misses me
already.
Oh. Chief!
Get down here now.
I'm not asking.
That's weird.
We received the following letter about
an hour ago. It has been authenticated.
It's from the Yin-Yang killer.
Pay close attention.
"Hey. everybody. I'm back.
for one night only.
"I'm going to kill
someone tonight.
"Guess who?
Guess where? Guess how?
"This is going
to be so much fun.
"Signed. Mr. Yang. "
He's looking for a new
challenger. That's what he does.
Chief. I believe
he's speaking to me.
Trust me. I'm ready.
Well. come on people. He
could be talking about anybody.
Look. just last week.
Officer Jankowicz guessed my
favorite variety of snack cracker.
Tuscan wheat.
it's really obscure.
I know. you know
That I'm not telling the truth
They just don't have any proof
Embrace the deception
Learn how to bend
Your worst inhibitions tend
to psych you out in the end
What do we have
on his description?
We don't. We've never had any age.
ethnicity or physical description.
The harsh truth
is that this is his game.
And we just have
to play along with him.
That's a terrific plan.
Especially since it's worked
out so well in the past.
Chief. the Mayor's
on the phone.
Oh. here we go.
Detective Lassiter.
introduce Shawn
to our point person.
Spencer. listen up.
Whoa. whoa. whoa.
Getting... I'm getting
something already.
What? What is it?
I can see the killer.
Already?
Yes.
And I know exactly
where he is.
Right there.
Come on. that's our guy.
Shawn.
Shawn. that is
Mary Lightly.
our profiler from the Serial
Homicide and Abduction Task Force.
He is very familiar with
the patterns of our killer.
And how to make an attractive
lamp out of human skin.
Shawn. play nice. He's a
genius. and we need him.
Mary. this is...
Shawn Spencer.
in the flesh.
See? He said "flesh. "
You know him? I've
done my research. okay?
Yeah. well.
I've Googled myself. too.
and there's a lot
of stuff missing.
This is my partner.
Sterling Cooper.
Hello.
So what's "Mary"
short for? Marion?
No.
Great.
we're all good friends.
Care to shed a little
light on this subject?
Mr. Yang is the most notorious
killer this city has never seen.
He claimed six victims
in the summer of 1995.
and has resurfaced twice. claiming
a single victim in each instance.
He only resurfaces when he
feels there's a worthy opponent.
Now. his M.O.
Is to challenge us
with the opportunity to save the
victims by solving his riddles.
Question. regarding
the whole Mary thing.
My father's name
was Mary.
His father before him
was named Mary.
and his father before him
was named Craig.
Fair enough. Proceed.
Yin-Yang.
The origin of this Chinese
symbol is the unity of opposites.
Two opposing. and at the same
time. complimentary aspects.
Dark versus light. Killer
versus cop. Kramer versus Kramer.
Just show him the riddle.
"She serves the General
well today
"whose soldiers
wait to die.
"In a white river
they shall pay
"for them she will not cry. Who is she?"
Now. this riddle came with
this stopwatch already running.
One of his classic moves.
We've got one hour
and ten minutes. people.
Generals and soldiers. She'd
be in the military. McNab!
Yes. sir!
Damn it.
I want you to contact every
military base in an 80-mile radius.
Find out if any female personnel
have gone AWOL in the last 48 hours.
And bear in mind. it's the
psychic that he wants to play with.
Each riddle will relate
to him. personally.
Do you have
any thoughts. Shawn?
Yes. Jules. I do.
First of all. his rhyming
skills are rudimentary at best.
"Today" and "pay"? "Die" and
"cry"? Come on. That's bush league.
It's
bush. Lassy!
Spencer. stop screwing
around. Get on with it.
I understand.
Yes. Thank you. sir.
Karen. you're not going
to use my son as a pawn.
Oh. I'll advise you
to proceed with caution.
Need I remind you
what happened
to the last detective who went
head-to-head with this sick bastard?
He lost. and
an innocent girl died.
Now. I will thank you to go
home and let us do our work!
Not going to happen.
Not going to happen!
Henry!
Your son is the only shot
that we have. Period.
Yeah. well.
not my problem.
Thus far...
Shawn!
Excuse me.
Hey. did I miss
a memo?
I thought Bring Your Daddy
to Work Day was next week.
I forbid you to be a part of
this. Shawn. You're coming with me.
Whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa.
Forbid me?
I'm familiar with your
hands-on approach to parenting.
but I'm not 27 anymore.
I can do whatever I want.
This guy
knows about you.
he knows about
everybody you care about.
Think about that.
You don't catch this
son of a bitch. kid.
you're never going
to sleep again.
Spencer. 55 minutes.
Go home. Dad.
I've got this.
Go home.
Sorry. guys. My dad was just
dropping off my Zodiac DVD.
Can we focus. please?
"In a white river
they shall pay. "
His seventh victim
washed up on shore.
Maybe there's a... No! There's
never a repeat performance.
Okay? Each victim
is a new masterpiece.
and the first riddle
is always a gimme.
This guy is itching
to play the game.
Think about
the last 24 hours.
Gus! Gus. I got it. I mean.
I know who the General is.
His name is Mills.
General Mills.
the cereal manufacturer?
Exactly! The white river is
milk. and the soldiers are cereal.
So who is she?
Hi. welcome to Captain
Ron's. Table for five?
There was a waitress here
earlier. long brown hair.
I haven't seen her in a
while. She must be on break.
Where? In the back. by the lockers.
How do you know
this girl?
We don't really know her.
She served us
our lunch.
"Oh. rats. Shawn. so close.
Too bad she has to die.
"But how? And when? And where?
Don't bother asking why. "
Well. he still
owes us a riddle.
This is just the amuse-bouche.
He's taunting you.
I believe he's using the
Alpha-Bits to send a message.
that he. too. believes that
breakfast for lunch is way underrated.
Would anyone like to try writing
this message with a burrito?
Open challenge.
Take a shot.
Exactly.
I rest my case.
And now
I want a burrito.
Can I talk to you
for a second. please?
Dude. what are you doing?
What are you talking about?
A girl's life is at stake
and you're acting like an ass?
Making jokes?
You haven't taken this thing
seriously from jump street.
Exactly.
Exactly?
Gus. I have to work
like this. okay?
That guy gets
in my head. we lose.
I have to do my thing.
I cannot show weakness.
And my fanciful rhetoric
helps defuse a situation
that's very tense
for the group.
But Shawn.
nobody is laughing.
Trust me. They're
laughing on the inside.
That's how
it works. buddy.
And I need you
to help me out here.
Do you think
you can do that?
I'll try.
All right.
"Little League is over.
You just became a pro.
"Score a run.
we'll have more fun.
"Make sure you
beat the throw. "
Next location.
How much time do we have?
Seventeen minutes.
Wow.
I want pancakes.
Who wants some pancakes?
Whipped butter.
Maple syrup. What?
"Make sure you beat the throw"
insinuates a close play.
You gotta touch
home plate.
You gotta touch home
plate to score a run.
That means the clue is back
at the police station.
Hmm. Mmm-hmm.
Make a hole!
Mom?
Hey. goose.
Hi. Mrs. Spencer.
Hey.
Spencer! Let's go!
We need to talk.
I'll make it quick.
Sure. no problem. Find the
clue. I'll be right there!
Bye.
Bye
I'm not going
to mince words.
Your father called me.
he's worried about you.
He wants me to convince
you not to do this.
So he calls you. you hop on a
plane. That's how it works. huh?
No. Shawn. I didn't
fly down here.
I was at a conference
in Ventura.
You were in town?
Would've been nice to know.
Truth is. I'm worried
about you. too.
I did psych evals
of several officers
who were involved in this first
round of this maniac's game.
It wasn't pretty.
All right. look.
first of all. Mom. I have
a date tonight. All right?
So I have to wrap this up
at a reasonable hour.
And secondly. this guy has
never gone up against me.
If I can stand here. and tell
you that I will nail this guy.
are you really going
to tell me to walk away?
Shawn!
Mom!
I can beat him.
I will
beat him.
Okay. goose. Nail
the son of a bitch.
Yeah. Okay.
I've got to go. Mom.
Please be right.
Spencer! Conference room. Thanks.
Well. someone must
have signed for this.
It wasn't delivered. Dobson
found it outside the file room.
Well. how
in the hell can...
Okay. you know what.
people? Eyes open!
Chief? Lou Sardocki from the
Independent is on the phone.
He says you owe him
a statement?
Oh. I'll give him a statement.
That's pretty clever.
"Meet my little
buddy Ben. "
"Pitter patter is your hint. If you can't
remember when. just read the fine print. "
And we have
less than one hour.
Shawn. can you
speak to it?
No. he can't
speak to it!
Yes. he can. Just give
him some room. Back up.
Fine. knock yourself
out. Doctor Dolittle.
"Doctor Dolittle"? I know you
can do better than that. Lassy.
I know you can.
I don't... I don't know what
I'm supposed to remember.
Hey. everybody.
Guess who I am?
Hee. hee
I'm Michael Jackson.
King of pop.
Shawn. I don't think this is working.
Are you kidding me? That was a
home run. Keep up the good work.
"Pitter patter"
is the hint.
Now. I don't think
we're speaking to a mouse.
I think the mouse
is speaking to you.
What do you got. Shawn?
"Fine print. "
Hello. my friend.
It's the fine print.
He was walking on it.
Dude. this is crazy!
"Adam Hornstock selling
black snake. Will go fast. "
"Mira Gaffney seeks Bruton
Gaster to love her tender. "
All people
from past cases.
How do you know that?
I told you.
I did my research.
And finding Bouchard's treasure
was extremely impressive.
Thank you. Willard.
My pleasure.
"Snarky psychic seeks ferroequinologist
to help with killer smile. "
He's calling me snarky?
"Ferroequinologist"?
A ferroequinologist
is a train enthusiast.
How do you know that?
Because I am
a ferroequinologist.
I too. am
"Love her tender. "
The tender is a small fuel car
right behind the locomotive.
And "black snake"
is slang for coal train.
There's only one coal train
that runs through Santa Barbara.
Thank God.
The train's right on
time. That is outstanding.
It's not
going to stop.
What?
It's not
going to stop.
This is just
a pull-through station.
What the hell
are we doing here?
Come on!
What the...
Where the hell
are you going?
Come on. Gus. This is our fantasy.
man! It's like we're hobos.
I don't have
a hobo fantasy. Shawn.
Abigail. you
called me back!
Yes. you left me very specific
instructions in your message to do so.
Is this a bad time?
No. I can talk!
Look. we're still
totally on for tonight.
I might just have to push
the time a little bit.
Uh-huh. Let me guess. you're
chasing a serial killer or something.
Holy crap. yes! Yes. that's
exactly what I'm doing! How did...
I cannot believe that you are
bailing on me again!
Hold on!
Tell Abigail
what we're doing!
Hello. Abigail!
It's Gus!
We're chasing
a train like hobos!
What?
She wants
to talk with you.
First of all. his
out-of-breath voice is terrible.
He was bad in Othello
senior year. he's bad now.
Look. I'm just flashing
back to high school.
and I have this image of me standing
alone on a pier looking like an idiot.
Look. I swear I'm
telling the truth!
I'm going to have
to call you back!
By the way. you were
beautiful on that pier!
Ah!
"A moving picture
is worth a thousand words.
"so read the story
and follow the birds.
"P.S. Once you're there
you'll hear a phone.
"You have eight rings
to pick up.
"or the girl is dead.
"Shame on me.
that didn't even rhyme. "
We have 27 minutes
to solve this.
Okay. Here. This is. uh...
Okay...
What do you see?
Nothing. I don't see
anything. Not yet.
Oh. wait. I do see
something. What? What is it?
I think you're going to want
to see this. It's pretty good.
Let me on.
Mary. I'm surprised
it took you so long.
You seemed to spry.
Ankle weights.
I always wear them.
Even when I sleep.
I read about it
in Men's Fitness.
Totally reinvigorated
Ryan Reynolds' career.
So what's the riddle?
How can I help?
"A moving...
A moving picture.
"A moving picture
is worth a thousand words. "
You've got to be kidding me.
You've got to be kidding me!
I got it!
I solved it! Let's go!
That's it! That's it!
"Follow the birds. "
There.
That's five rings.
Shawn! Answer it!
Shawn. what
are you doing?
No. don't you see? It didn't start
ringing until we were three feet away.
Answer the phone.
Spencer!
He's watching us
right now from somewhere!
Answer the phone. Shawn!
If that girl dies. you're
an accessory to murder.
Shawn. I hope to God
you know what you're doing.
Unbelievable.
He's been here.
He was here watching us
the whole time!
Don't touch anything.
Let's get CSI down here
to dust for prints.
There's no need.
I'm sure he touched things.
He probably touched
everything.
but you're not going to find any
prints. He's too good for that.
What is this sick. twisted admiration
you have for this whack job?
Now do you get
how good he is?
This puppy's
just warming up.
Hey everybody. check it out.
Look how big I am
compared to this plane.
I'm King Kong.
Guster. what the hell
is going on with you?
Seriously. man. I need you
to pull yourself together.
Oh. my God.
Let me see that.
I got it!
It's a message.
He says. "You are a
naughty. naughty boy. "
He's giving us another
chance. She's still alive.
Let's go back to the station.
wait for instructions.
Forget that.
I'm... I'm not going.
What do you mean?
I'm nobody's puppet. okay?
I'm done. I'm done
playing his little game.
I solved his puzzles. I talked
to a rat. I even chased a train.
I'm finished.
No one's ever gotten this far.
That's why he's still playing.
It's a sign of respect.
No. It isn't. Mary.
You said it. man.
with your fey name and
your weird Ken Burns haircut.
He's too good!
Isn't that right?
He's better than me!
We never had a chance! He's going
to kill that girl either way!
Maybe. maybe not. Shawn. but I
know this. you don't just give up.
Tell you what. Jules. uh. the next time
a serial killer calls you out. personally.
you can pick up
your little pompoms
and you can rally the troops
and never say die.
I'm out.
Now. get out.
All three of you.
I can't believe
I'm hearing this.
Should I
say it again?
You know what? Screw you.
Spencer. We don't need you!
We don't need him. O'Hara. We
will find this sicko on our own.
Come on!
We're running out of time.
Look. Shawn. I know you're
upset. but if we give up now...
Gus. don't be The Last of the
Famous International Playboys.
We're not giving up. okay?
Far from it.
The only chance we have
to win the game at this point
is to change
the rules. okay?
I took a risk out there because
I knew he wouldn't kill her.
I knew he wouldn't kill her
because he loves the game too much.
but that bought us time. It bought
us time to work by ourselves.
Okay? We're going to... We're
going to drop off his radar.
We're still going
to find the girl.
We're going to do it
on our own. That's our move.
All right.
but where do we start?
We go back
to the beginning.
Back to the beginning. and we
trace the steps of Mr. Yang.
All right. You like what
I did with the King Kong?
You're on fire.
You're even using props.
Just got this fax. Traced
it to a bogus 800 number.
"I'm no Doubting Thomas.
I pucker up to fights.
"Were you to shake my hand. you'd
have to use your right. Who am I?"
Well. if Yang was watching. he
couldn't know if Spencer flew the coop.
This could be directed
at any one of us.
Probably not
this guy.
It's me.
It's directed at me.
He must know
I'm a Civil War buff.
1863. Confederate General
Thomas "Stonewall" Jackson
was shot and killed by his own troops
at the Battle of Chancellorsville.
He was known for sucking on
lemons. even during combat.
And while he is buried
in Lexington. Virginia.
his left arm is buried
separately near the battlefield.
Hey. you guys remember that Pat
Swayze miniseries. North and South?
Talk about
Civil War buff. huh?
Oh. my God!
The Stonewall Hotel and
Suites! Probably room 1863!
We've got to get
down there.
And you can count me in for
next year's reenactment. partner.
Copy that.
Get my jacket.
Look. call me back. okay?
We're still on for tonight.
Gus and I are making some
serious progress here.
Call me back!
Straight to voicemail.
That's not a good sign.
Wrong! I drive a Jeep. A black Jeep.
Gus. there's no Jeep. I think
he drove away in her car.
We find the car.
we may find the girl.
Lassiter. hold on.
Find the girl's car.
It's a black Jeep.
We already did.
You got to get down here.
Where are you?
SBPD!
Room's clear!
Clear!
She's breathing.
I'll get the paramedics.
What is this?
"Shawn no longer
wants to play.
"Stakes too low
to make you stay"?
He's... He's got her. Gus.
He's got my mom.
Okay. I sent
a couple of officers
over to Abigail Lytar's
apartment. and she's fine.
But I'm posting them on a watch until
we can figure out what is going on.
Spencer.
you need to get in here.
"You should be moving.
as most people do.
"but instead you sit
and enjoy the view.
"P.S. Mommy says. 'Hi'
and 'Bye'.
Just in case. "
"VU." Why did he
spell it that way?
Maybe that's the hint.
Or maybe he
ran out of lipstick.
Brendan Vu.
From the spelling bee.
Good guess.
but it's a misdirect.
I know exactly what
he wants me to watch.
You do?
This is like
a needle in a haystack
made completely
out of needles.
Looks like we're
at the end game.
All right. we know he used the waitress's
car. so there's a good chance...
It's definitely a chance. What
kind of car does your wife drive?
She rents when
she's down here.
Do you know what company she rents from?
That could narrow it
down to a few models.
It's blue.
It's blue. Gus. We're looking
for a blue car. It's a sedan.
People. we're looking for a
blue car! A sedan! Go. go. go!
All right. split up.
Squad. cover the exits!
West side! West side!
Roger that.
Hey. man! Watch
where you're going!
Hey! Get off!
Get off the car!
Get off my car. man!
Hey. Ma.
Shawn! Shawn! Shh. shh!
Dad. get down. get down.
Oh. jeez.
Mom.
I'm going to take
this off. okay?
Mmm.
It's okay.
It's just a decoy.
I know. I see that.
He's fine. He's breathing.
Yang must have knocked him out.
SWAT. call for a medic!
Yes. ma'am.
Oh. my God.
Dad. she's strapped.
Oh. God. no.
Mom. where is he?
Maddie.
Henry?
Yeah. it's me. sweetheart. I'm
right here. I'm not going anywhere.
All right. then
I won't. either.
Besides. I don't really have
anything better to do right now.
It's just a pen.
It's just a pen!
What does this mean.
Mary? Tell us!
I don't know. This feels more like
improvisation. This isn't his game.
We got here in time.
Maybe we won.
No. he's definitely going to kill
her dead. I just don't know how.
He's been one step
ahead this whole time.
Where's Shawn?
Hopefully one step
ahead of us.
Okay.
All right. be honest with
me. You're surprised. right?
I'm prettier than
you thought I'd be.
It's the bone structure.
I won. I beat you. That
was the deal. Let my mom go.
You are just amazing.
Just my most.
most admirable foe.
But then. see. I knew you would
be. That's why I chose you.
Because I'm...
I'm your yin.
Well. that's sweet.
Thank you for that.
But you're completely
surrounded.
There's no way
out of this for you.
Hey. you know what I love about this
movie. Shawn? Its great resolution.
Okay. so call me
old-fashioned.
but really. is there anything more
satisfying than a solid ending?
You call me a killer. but the
truth is. I complete things.
And that is what people
really want. to feel complete.
That. and
a corner booth.
And now. our story. that we
created so beautifully together.
is going to end.
But how?
Do you want to know
what it is?
Or do you want
to be surprised?
Let's dial up!
Move in slow.
Stand down! Stand down!
Stand down. Stand down.
Move them back. Let's go!
Let me guess.
You want to die. right?
That's the perfect
resolution?
Gee. that's original.
You're a cliché.
You're a knockoff
of a knockoff.
I could have killed your
mom hours ago. Shawn.
This switch has such a light
touch. like pinching a baby's cheek.
And then. boom!
She blows up.
How much fun would
that be to see?
Oh. it gives me shivers.
I want to do that so badly!
But then.
you wouldn't like me. Shawn.
And I want you to like me.
Oh. God. I'm so torn.
I need you to like me. because we're
going to be working together again.
Oh. no. no. no. no.
You're going to rot in a cell
with four padded walls. The end.
No. The end
of the beginning.
I'm going to write
a book.
Our story.
It's going to be epic.
A bestseller.
And guess what? I want
you to write the forward.
Pass.
Okay.
But think about it
on your date tonight.
Clear!
Take the subject!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go!
Let's go.
Okay.
All right. you're okay.
You're okay. All right.
Think about it
on your date tonight.
She was there. Gus. she
was there the whole time.
You got her. Shawn.
End of story.
Congratulations.
Spencer.
Don't be too excited
there. Mary.
It's not like
we just apprehended
Santa Barbara's most
notorious killer or anything.
You're right. Gus. I'm sorry
to fly off the handle.
I've spent the last 13 years
of my life with this person.
I have to find a new hobby.
Two words.
Racquetball.
That could work.
Thanks for your help. man. I needed it.
Gus. you play racquetball?
Goodbye. Mary.
Until next time.
Okay. Okay.
There we go.
Better?
Henry. I told him
to go for it.
That doesn't matter.
What matters is that
you're both okay.
You two are the most important
people in the world to me. you know.
I do know.
Mom! Let's get you
out of here.
What do you need?
What can I do?
Let's see. You already got me
kidnapped by a raging sociopath...
Right. Check.
What else?
Nothing! Nothing.
goose. I'm really fine.
Your father's been taking
very good care of me.
Well. be good.
Yep.
If I'm not mistaken. you have
a very important date tonight.
Oh. Mom. please.
I can reschedule.
No. you won't!
I'm fine!
The crazy bitch snuck up from
behind me with chloroform.
Life is more than
catching bad guys.
You did a good
deed today.
Now it's time
to go see about a girl.
It's time to go see
about a...
How you like
them apples?
Well played. Mom.
All right.
Hey.
Shawn. did you really
just catch Mr. Yang?
Yes. I did. And he
turned out to be a she.
Curious.
Yeah.
Hey. I'm sorry I didn't
believe you earlier. I just. uh.
really didn't.
Half-apology
accepted.
Uh. I cut a deal with
the theater manager.
so this is still happening
in a big. big way.
How do you feel
about popped corn?
I like it.
I like it very much.
Jules! What are you
doing here?
What I mean is. you know.
who's going to fit Mr. Yang
with her straightjacket
and iron mask with face grill?
Something tells me there's
an entire precinct of officers
bidding on that job
right now.
Uh. can I interest you
in a Necco Wafer?
Shawn. can you just not
talk for a few seconds?
Look. I just wanted to tell
you that what you did today...
I mean. I can't imagine being
able to function at that level
while your mom
was... You know.
I am. uh. clearly not as
good with words as you are.
and I know that
things between us
have been
a little complicated.
and that there have probably been
some mixed signals. mostly from me.
with regards to the time that we spend
together outside of the line of duty.
Look. Jules...
Shh! Please. just let me
finish stumbling through this.
I'm almost done.
I promise.
What I'm saying
is that I think. maybe.
the best things.
the richest things.
aren't supposed
to come easily.
and that sometimes the moments
that make the most sense
happen when everything
else doesn't. and. well.
I think you deserve more
than popcorn tonight.
So why don't you let me
take you to dinner?
Detective O'Hara. are you
asking me out on a date?
I am.
A proper one.
Wow.
I cannot believe this.
All this time. and...
Your timing
is just awful.
It is?
Yeah. just dreadful.
What?
I can't go to dinner with you.
Jules. I'm already on a date.
You are? What. here?
Yeah. Right now.
It's... It's weird. it's
a little weird. but. uh...
Yeah.
With Abigail.
The one that got away.
Yeah.
Get out there.
She's not going
to wait forever.
Jules?
I am so sorry
for snapping at you earlier.
I know.
You all right?
Yeah. Why would you
even ask that?
Mostly because you look like
you got punched in the stomach
and stopped breathing
for a few seconds.
Wow. I didn't realize
I was that transparent.
The truth... The truth is.
Abigail. everything is not okay.
And I don't know
exactly how to say this.
Try using words
to form a sentence.
I'm so. so sorry. Abigail.
They're all out of butter.
Wait. what?
I know. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I don't know why
I'm apologizing.
'cause it's not my fault. really.
but I mean. it's opening night.
and how do you run out of
butter? That's cardinal.
That's cardinal.
What are we going to do?
I don't know exactly.
Uh. as you can see.
the kernels are fluffy.
and salted quite nicely.
I tried... I tried one.
But we do have Necco Wafers.
Necco?
And Toblerone.
I love Toblerone.
Yes. I sensed
that you might.
It's like a more sophisticated Krackle.
Yeah!
Hey. you're sure
about this?
Absolutely.
Now. in with you
into this carriage.
Okey-doke.
That's what
I'm talking about.
Gus.
Hello. Abigail.
The thing is.
it's his car.
It's a company car. and
he's very protective of it.
So just pretend
like he isn't here.
Are those
Necco Wafers up there?
Yes. they are. Pass them back please.
In between the lines
there's a lot of obscurity
I'm not inclined
to resign to maturity
If it's all right
then you're all wrong
But why bounce around
to the same damn song?
You'd rather run
when you can't crawl
I know. you know
That I'm not telling the truth
They just don't have any proof
Embrace the deception
Learn how to bend
Your worst inhibitions tend
to psych you out in the end
I know. you know
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-